- Ow! - You don't just dump chemicals into a beaker willy-nilly.
- Well, I'm tired of all the waity-waity.
Let's get to the dumpy-dumpy.
- Safety first.
Goggles. - Chill.
If I wear goggles, how are the ladies gonna see my eyes?
- Goggles!
- Fine.
Hey, babe.
Let's make science.
- Are we done, children?
- 我们完成了吗，孩子们？
Can we let the science fair winner--
我们可以让科学展的获胜者——
- Runner-up. - It's under review!
- 亚军。 - 还在评审中！
I have a process, Dawn.
我有一个流程，Dawn。
- Well, here's my process.
- 好吧，这是我的流程。
- Willy-nilly! Willy-nilly!
- 随便！随便！
[bubbling]
[冒泡声]
- Fools!
- 傻瓜！
- Science is awesome.
- 科学真棒。
- Look what you did! - Me?
- 看看你做了什么！ - 我？
You're the science fair runner-up!
你是科学展览会的亚军！
That's what you get for waiting.
这就是你拖延的后果。
- That foam is going to give you rashes!
那泡沫会让你起疹子的！
- Yeah? Well, happy scratching!
是吗？那就好好挠痒吧！
- [screams]
（尖叫）
- [laughs]
（笑）
- For crying out loud, you could have gotten rashes!
真是的，你本来可能会起疹子的！
- I told you.
我告诉过你。
- Nicky.
尼基。
There is nothing here for any of you to be proud of.
这里没有什么值得你们任何人骄傲的。
Now, I've called your parents.
现在，我已经叫了你们的父母。
- Oh, come on. - Really?
- 哦，拜托。 - 真的吗？
- Don't do that! - Save it.
- 别这样！ - 省省吧。
You can answer to them.
你们可以向他们解释。
[knocks on door]
（敲门声）
Come in!
进来！
All: Hey, Mom.
大家：嘿，妈妈。
Hey, Dad.
嘿，爸爸。
[upbeat rock music]
（欢快的摇滚音乐）
♪ ♪
- [whistling]
- One, two, three, four!
一，二，三，四！
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na ♪
呐，呐，呐
♪ Na na-na ♪
呐呐呐
♪ Na, na, na ♪
呐，呐，呐
♪ Na na-na ♪
呐呐呐
- One, two!
一，二！
One, two, three, four!
一，二，三，四！
- ♪ Hey hey hey hey ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
[buzzer]
- This is the third time this month
- 这是这个月第三次
we've been called away from the store
我们从店里被叫出来
to come pick you kids up.
来接你们这些孩子。
- Sounds like quality family time to me.
- 听起来像是我们家的优质时光。
Am I right?
我说得对吗？
Up top.
击个掌。
Comin' down.
下来。
- You know, every time I get a call from the school,
- 你知道，每次学校给我打电话，
I keep hoping that it is finally that call that says,
我总是希望那是最终的电话，
"Mrs. Harper, your quadruplets are amazing
说：“哈珀太太，您的四胞胎太棒了，
and they are working together,
他们正在合作，
and they are definitely not having a wet toilet paper war
而且他们肯定没有在残疾人厕所里用湿卫生纸打仗。”
in the handicapped stall."
但从来不是。从来不是！
But it never is. It never is!
- 是他们的错！
- It's their fault!
一切总是得按他们的方式来。
Everything always has to be their way.
- 好吧，如果我关心我的成绩，我很抱歉。 - 如果我不关心，我也抱歉。
- Well, I'm sorry if I care about my grades. - And I'm sorry if I don't.
- 好吧，如果我在乎我的成绩，我很抱歉。 - 如果我不在乎，我也抱歉。
- I'm sorry I bit you all in the womb!
- 抱歉我在子宫里咬了你们所有人！
[all speaking at once]
[大家同时说话]
- Wait, wait. Guys. Guys. Okay, wait, wait, wait. Give me a--okay, kids. Hey, quiet!
- 等等，等等。伙计们。伙计们。好了，等等，等等。给我一个--好了，孩子们。嘿，安静！
Wow, that finally worked.
哇，这终于奏效了。
- The problem is, you kids can't do anything together
- 问题是，你们这些孩子在一起什么都做不了
without getting at each other's throats.
而不互相掐脖子。
- Oh, his throat.
- 哦，他的脖子。
[crack] - Good tip. - Get out of the way! - Enough!
[咔嚓] - 好建议。 - 让开！ - 够了！
I gave birth to a team.
我生了一队人。
What happened to my team?
我的团队怎么了？
- We can't be a team if they don't follow their leader.
- 如果他们不跟随领导者，我们就不能成为一个团队。
- I'm the leader.
- 我是领导者。
I'm the oldest. - By four seconds.
我是最年长的。 - 只比我大四秒。
- I learned a lot in those four seconds.
- 在那四秒钟里，我学到了很多。
- You learn anything about rashes?
- 你学到了关于皮疹的知识吗？
[all groan]
[大家都叹气]
- You see what I'm dealing with?
- 你们看到我面对的是什么了吗？
It's not like we're bad kids.
我们并不是坏孩子。
Bad things just... happen to us.
只是坏事总是发生在我们身上。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- See?
- 看到了吧？
Our lives are so unfair.
我们的生活太不公平了。
- Hey, Mom.
- 嘿，妈妈。
Dad.
爸爸。
- Okay, Kenny, we have told you not to call us that.
- 好吧，肯尼，我们告诉过你不要那样叫我们。
We are not your parents.
我们不是你的父母。
It's creepy.
那样很吓人。
- But they call you that.
- 但他们那样叫你们。
- 'Cause we're their children.
- 因为我们是他们的孩子。
- We're quadruplets.
我们是四胞胎。
- Quadruplets?
四胞胎？
I look more like you two than him.
我看起来更像你们两个，而不是他。
Anyway, Pops, this came for ya.
不管怎样，老爸，这是给你的。
- Yes! It's here!
是的！它来了！
Behold.
看好了。
This jersey was worn by Brownie Wilson,
这件球衣是布朗尼·威尔逊穿过的，
fabled hero of the Gridiron from days of Yore.
他是传说中的橄榄球英雄，来自古老的年代。
I searched long and hard for this jersey,
我花了很长时间和精力寻找这件球衣，
and now, she's mine.
现在，她是我的了。
- Wow, he even signed it and everything.
哇，他甚至签了名。
- No one touches my number 2.
没人能碰我的2号。
- [laughs]
[笑]
Number two.
2号。
- This is the greatest day of my life.
这是我人生中最伟大的一天。
- Our wedding? The kids' birth?
我们的婚礼？孩子们的出生？
- Oh, come on, you think anybody ever says,
哦，得了吧，你觉得有人会说，
"Yay, four kids at once"?
“耶，一次生了四个孩子”？
Okay, change of subject.
好吧，换个话题。
Punishment time. Who wants to clean up the puke in the skydiving simulator?
惩罚时间。谁想清理跳伞模拟器里的呕吐物？
- You know what?
你知道吗？
As the oldest--
作为最大的那个——
- By four seconds!
只大四秒！
- I will show my little brothers how to be
我要教我的小弟弟们如何
grown up, responsible,
成熟、负责任、
and mature.
成为一个大人。
[barks]
[吠叫]
Puppy!
小狗！
Look at this little snudger!
看看这个小家伙！
I just wanna eat his face!
我真想吃了他的脸！
Yes, I do!
是的，我确实！
- These kids cannot focus.
这些孩子无法集中注意力。
Tom, help me out here.
汤姆，帮帮我。
- Who's my sweet number 2?
谁是我的甜心二号？
Oh, stop! Stop it!
哦，别这样！别闹了！
- I'm having a pet adoption fair in the lot next door.
我正在隔壁空地举办宠物领养集市。
- Boom, adopted. - Yeah.
嘭，领养了。
- Boom, returned.
是的。
You kids can't take care of a dog.
嘭，又退回了。
It would just turn into one big fight.
你们这些孩子照顾不了狗的。
- Fight? Pfft.
Fight.
We're totally buds.
Quad hug!
- You have nice eyes. - I love us.
- You're feelin' it, right?
- That felt forced.
- Forced? Pfft.
Forced.
Ricky, tell him why it's not forced.
- Mom, Dad, you've always taught us
that love means trusting each other.
So if you really love us,
isn't it time you trusted us?
Nicky, back me up here.
- Look, I trust this dog is gonna give us worms.
But he'll give us worms together.
- Together. - Yes!
- Wormy is right.
We can totes do this.
- No, and you're gonna give the dog right back to--
不，你会把狗直接还给——
[gasps]
（吸气声）
He is so soft!
他太软了！
- You guys are not ready for this.
你们还没准备好面对这个。
- Mom, I know we've disappointed you in the past,
妈妈，我知道我们过去让你失望了，
but this dog is a chance
但这条狗是一个机会
for us to show you that we can work together.
让我们向你证明我们可以一起合作。
Please let us prove that we can be the team
请让我们证明我们可以成为
that you want us to be.
你希望我们成为的团队。
Please?
请答应我们，好吗？
Mommy?
妈妈？
- All right.
- 好吧。
You can have the dog.
你们可以养这只狗。
- Yeah! Fireworks!
- 耶！太好了！
- But...this is a trial run.
- 但是...这是个试养期。
You have one week to show that you guys can do this together.
你们有一周时间来证明你们能一起照顾好它。
If not, then he's gotta go back to the shelter.
如果不行，它就得送回收容所了。
Got it? - Yep!
明白了吗？- 没问题！
- Yes. - Got it.
- 是的。- 明白了。
- Word. - Great, I'll get his papers.
- 没错。- 太好了，我去拿它的文件。
- [gasps]
- [倒抽一口气]
He can read!
他会读!
- Harper huddle!
- Harper，集合！
All: Ah, Harper!
所有人: 啊，Harper！
- I totally deserved that.
- 我完全应得那个。
- I'm not gonna lie.
- 我不打算撒谎。
You rock those better than me.
你穿那些比我好看。
- Dicky.
- Dicky。
We have to take this seriously,
我们必须认真对待这件事，
and that's why I've come up with a schedule
这就是为什么我制定了一个狗狗照顾职责的计划
of doggy caretaking duties.
狗狗照顾任务的安排。
Ta-da!
塔-达！
- That's a very nice chore chart.
- 这是一个非常漂亮的任务表。
Of course it's not as nice as mine.
当然，没有我的漂亮。
Ta-double-da.
塔-双达。
- Wow.
- 哇。
Those four seconds are really killing you, aren't they?
那四秒钟真的让你很难受，不是吗？
- I just think my way
- 我只是认为我的方法
is the best way of taking of care of Chip.
是照顾奇普的最佳方式。
- [buzzer sound] Ehh! We're not naming him Chip.
- [蜂鸣声] 呃！我们不叫他奇普。
- That's right. His name is Tiny Elvis.
- 没错。他的名字是小埃尔维斯。
- He doesn't look anything like Elvis.
- 他看起来一点也不像埃尔维斯。
- He will when I put him in...
- 我给他穿上这个之后，他就会像了...
This.
这件。
- Um, he's not wearing that.
- 呃，他不会穿那个的。
He's wearing...this.
他会穿...这个。
And his name is Admiral Squishy Paws.
他的名字是海军上将软爪。
- Clearly he's a Gary!
- 显然他是个加里！
All: Gary?
所有人: 加里？
[all speaking at once]
[所有人同时说话]
- Gary stinks! - It's the perfect name.
- Gary臭死了！ - 这名字太合适了。
- He's Tiny Elvis!
- 他是迷你版猫王！
- [whistles]
- [吹口哨]
We're doing exactly what Mom and Dad said we would.
我们正在做爸爸妈妈说我们会做的事。
- Sweet. - No, not sweet.
- 真棒。 - 不，不是棒。
We have to work together.
我们必须一起合作。
That's why I'm willing to follow...
这就是为什么我愿意跟随...
[gagging]
[作呕]
Ricky's lead.
Ricky的领导。
- I thought you might,
- 我就知道你会，
and that's why I created a picture to represent that.
这就是为什么我创作了一幅画来代表这一点。
- This is gonna be totally easy.
- 这将会非常简单。
This is so hard.
这太难了。
- This is the longest week ever.
- 这是有史以来最长的一周。
- It's only been two hours.
- 才过了两个小时。
[dog whining] - He needs to go out.
[狗在呜咽] - 他需要出去。
- How can you tell?
- 你怎么知道的？
[whines]
[呜咽声]
- Those are his "I have to pee" ears.
- 那是他的“我得尿尿”耳朵。
- It's not my turn to walk him.
- 不是我带他散步的时候。
- Not mine. - Not mine.
- Ugh, I guess I'll be the responsible one.
- No way, I'm the leader.
I'm the responsible one.
- Don't you be more responsible than me!
- Hold on!
It's cape weather!
- Man, they're so easy.
- It's wonderful, isn't it?
- It's overwhelming.
- [sighs]
叹气
This week has been amazing.
这周真是太棒了。
- Glorious.
辉煌。
- I just never thought I'd see this day.
我从没想过会看到这一天。
- It's like a dream come true.
这就像梦想成真一样。
[both sniffling, sighing]
两人抽泣，叹息
Love you, Brownie.
爱你，布朗尼。
- Is Mom still looking over here?
妈妈还在看这边吗？
- I can't fake this smile much longer.
我装不出这个笑容了。
- I'm so sick of you guys...
我真是受够你们了...
But if we make it through today,
但如果我们今天能挺过去，
Squishy Paws will be staying with us forever.
Squishy Paws 就会永远和我们在一起。
- I think the person who's actually done his chores all week
- 我觉得这周真正完成了所有家务的人
should get to name the dog.
应该有权给狗取名。
- I thought we settled on Gary.
- 我以为我们决定叫它Gary了。
- And she's gone.
- 她走了。
- Gary is not a dog name.
- Gary不是个狗的名字。
- It's better than Tiny Elvis.
- 总比Tiny Elvis好。
- Well, this foam bat says it isn't.
- 好吧，这个泡沫棒说不。
- [hoarsely] Let's end this.
- [沙哑地] 让我们结束这一切。
- Quad bat fight!
四人棒球大战！
- Aah! Gary!
啊！加里！
- Tiny Elvis! - Gary! [overlapping shouting]
小埃尔维斯！ - 加里！[重叠的喊叫]
- Chip! Chip! [overlapping shouts]
奇普！奇普！[重叠的喊叫]
- Tiny Elvis!
小埃尔维斯！
- Tiny El--
小埃尔--
both: No! - Dad's jersey!
不！ - 爸爸的球衣！
- Oh, no!
哦，不！
- Phew, that was close. - Phew.
呼，好险。 - 呼。
- Phew. - Sorry, Hazel.
呼。 - 对不起，黑兹尔。
- Uh--I'm okay.
- 呃——我没事。
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
- Look what you did!
- 看看你做了什么！
- You called quad bat fight!
- 你引发了四人棒球大战！
- You started it! - You started it--
- 是你先开始的！ - 是你先开始的——
[gasps]
[倒抽气]
- Oh, no.
- 哦，不。
- At least his ears aren't-- uh...
- 至少他的耳朵没有——呃...
- Put down your pee ears and step away from the jersey.
- 放下你的耳朵，远离那件球衣。
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
[urine pattering] [all groan]
[尿液滴落声] [所有人呻吟]
- Is it coming off?
- 尿渍能洗掉吗？
- [hacks] I can't tell over the smell of your lunch.
- [咳嗽] 我闻着你的午饭味儿，分辨不出来。
Can you maybe lean back until you hit a mint?
你能不能往后靠，直到碰到薄荷味的东西？
- No big deal.
- 没什么大不了的。
Chip just went number one on dad's number 2.
奇普刚刚在爸爸的2号球衣上解决了1号问题。
- Normally I'd laugh at that, but--
- 通常我会笑的，但是——
no, it's still funny.
不，这还是挺好笑的。
- No, it's not.
- 不，这一点都不好笑。
My life is over.
我的生活完蛋了。
- Come on, you guys!
拜托，各位！
If we handle this right, dad doesn't have to find out,
只要我们处理得当，爸爸没必要知道，
and we get to keep the dog.
而且我们还能继续养这条狗。
- What's the point?
有什么意义呢？
- It's over. - I failed.
一切都结束了。- 我失败了。
I'm a horrible leader!
我是个糟糕的领导！
[thwack] All: Ow!
哎哟！
- You could have used the side without the price tag.
你可以不用贴着价签那面打。
- We're Harpers.
我们可是哈珀家的人。
Did we give up when Nicky got his head stuck in the railing?
尼克把头卡在栏杆里时，我们放弃了吗？
Did we give up when Dicky got his head stuck in the railing?
当迪基的头卡在栏杆里时，我们有放弃吗？
Did we give up when we were having trouble
当我们遇到困难时，
getting Ricky's head stuck in the railing?
试图让瑞奇的头卡在栏杆里时，我们有放弃吗？
No! So we're not giving up now!
没有！所以我们现在也不会放弃！
We may have failed each other,
我们可能彼此失败了，
but for the first time in our lives,
但在我们生命中第一次，
we need to think of something bigger than the four of us.
我们需要考虑比我们四个人更大的事情。
This guy.
这个人。
He deserves a good home, even if we don't deserve him.
他值得一个好家，即使我们不配拥有他。
- [sniffles]
- [抽泣]
All: Ah, Harper!
所有人: 啊, 哈珀!
- So this is programmed to control the snowball launcher
- 所以这是用来控制冬季运动区的雪球发射器, 嗯?
in the winter sports area, hmm?
从现在开始, 肯尼...
And from now on, Kenny...
你负责...
You're in...
管理它。
Charge of it.
好样的。
Good stuff.
- 好了, 尼基, 里基。
- All right, Nicky, Ricky.
你们两个把球衣带回家清洗。
You two take the jersey home and clean it.
迪基, 你遛狗。
Dicky, you walk the dog.
我会让爸爸远离这里直到你们回来。
I'll keep dad away from this until you get back.
我会拖住爸爸，直到你们回来。
Hurry!
快点！
- Hey, kiddo. What's up with the blanket?
- 嘿，孩子。这毯子是怎么回事？
- Oh, I was just doing a little research on antique jerseys,
- 哦，我只是在对古董球衣做一点研究,
and it turns out they fade
结果发现它们如果暴露在太多阳光下就会褪色。
if they're exposed to too much sunlight.
那些往日的痕迹会从你的旧2号球衣上消失无踪。
It'll wash those days of yore right off your old number 2.
所以在危险过去之前，
So until the danger's passed,
我要给她好好盖上毯子保护起来。
I'm gonna blanket her up real nice.
- 谢谢你，亲爱的。
- Thank you, honey.
你知道吗，这种责任感
You know, that's the kind of responsibility
你知道，那种责任感
that's gonna make Gary Chip Tiny Elvis Squishy Paws
会让Gary、Chip、Tiny Elvis、Squishy Paws
a permanent part of this family.
成为这个家庭永久的一员。
- You can count on me, Dad!
——你可以信赖我，爸爸！
- Hey, ladies. You like puppies?
——嘿，女士们。你们喜欢小狗吗？
- It's 1:19.
——现在是1点19分。
They've been gone so long,
他们离开太久了，
it's like time is moving backwards.
感觉时间都在倒流。
- You're holding your phone upside down.
——你把手机拿倒了。
- It's 6:11!
——是6点11分！
Finally! - Sorry.
终于！ - 对不起。
Mom was home, so we had to go to the laundromat.
妈妈在家，所以我们得去自助洗衣店。
- Is it clean?
- 干净吗？
- Not bad for such a busy place.
- 对于这么忙的地方来说还不错。
- Not the laundromat, the shirt!
- 不是洗衣店，是衬衫！
It looks great!
看起来很棒！
- Where's the signature?
- 签名呢？
- It must have washed off!
- 肯定洗掉了！
- Oh, I knew that machine was too strong.
- 哦，我就知道那机器太强劲了。
That delicate setting is a joke!
那个精致的设置就是个笑话！
- Okay, so we just need to re-write the signature.
- 好吧，我们只需要重新写上签名。
- Wait, before you do anything--
- 等等，在你做任何事之前——
- No more waity-waity.
- 别再等等了。
I've been looking at that signature all week.
我整个星期都在看那个签名。
Brownie Wilson's signature is burned into my brain.
布朗尼·威尔逊的签名已经深深印在我的脑海里。
There.
好了。
- Who's Brownie Squishy Paws?
- 布朗尼·斯奎什·帕斯是谁？
- You wrote, "Brownie Squishy Paws."
- 你写的是‘布朗尼·斯奎什·帕斯’。
- It just came out! - Why would that just come out?
- 它就这么出来了！ - 为什么会这样？
- I practiced that name all day!
- 我一整天都在练习那个名字！
- You want the price tag or all leather?
- 你要价签还是全皮？
- It's over.
- 结束了。
That's it.
- 就这样。
I failed.
- 我失败了。
I'm sorry, Squishy Paws.
- 对不起，Squishy Paws。
I let you down.
- 我让你失望了。
- You're giving up?
- 你要放弃吗？
- Where's the girl who rubbed butter on my face to pop me out of that railing?
- 那个用黄油帮我从栏杆里出来的女孩去哪儿了？
- And where's the girl who decided to stop pulling
- 还有那个决定不再拉我而是直接把我推过栏杆的女孩呢？
and just push me right through that railing?
还有那个决定不再拉我，而是直接把我推过栏杆的女孩呢？
- And where's the girl who pinned my arms down
- 还有那个按住我的手臂
while Dicky and Nicky jammed my head into that railing
让迪基和尼基把我的头塞进栏杆里
for laughing at them?
因为我嘲笑他们的那个女孩呢？
- I'm right here.
- 我就在这儿。
- Good, 'cause our team could kind of use a leader.
- 很好，因为我们团队现在有点需要一个领导者。
- Nicky, can you get the marker out?
- 尼基，你能把标记笔拿出来吗？
- I say this with full certainty:
- 我这么说是有十足把握的：
possibly.
可能吧。
To the cafe!
去咖啡馆！
This is my own formula.
这是我的独创配方。
It's super strong, so a few drops is all we need.
它非常强力，所以我们只需要几滴。
[liquid splats]
[screams]
[all screaming]
- Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
[all screaming]
- [screams]
Why are we screaming?
我们为什么要尖叫？
- Oh, we're just, uh...
哦，我们只是，呃...
Super excited about all these new smoothie options.
对所有这些新的 smoothie 选项超级兴奋。
- Yes, like mango-squash-onion.
- 是的，比如芒果-南瓜-洋葱。
[screams]
[尖叫]
- Hey, who's thirsty?
- 嘿，谁渴了？
- Well, not Ricky, because he has some important work things
- 哦，Ricky 不渴，因为他有重要工作要做，
to do all the way over there.
就在那边。
- Yep. Work, work, work.
- 对，工作，工作，工作。
- He's a great kid.
- 他是个好孩子。
You know, we almost named him Gary,
你知道，我们差点给他取名叫Gary，
but we couldn't think of three other names that rhymed with it.
但我们想不出另外三个与之押韵的名字。
- Larry. - Carrie.
- 拉里。 - 凯莉。
- Harry.
- 哈里。
- Oh, Mom!
- 哦，妈妈！
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
- I just came to see my amazing kids.
- 我只是来看看我那了不起的孩子们。
- And now you see one. Now you don't.
- 现在你看到一个了。现在你又看不到了。
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- 嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Come here, I need a hug!
过来，我需要一个拥抱！
Wait, wait.
等等，等等。
What's under your shirt?
你衬衫下面是什么？
- What? No, I didn't.
- 什么？不，我没有。
- We have to rescue Ricky.
- 我们必须救出Ricky。
- Why are you acting so strange?
- 你为什么表现得这么奇怪？
Just show me what's in your shirt.
就给我看看你衬衫里有什么。
- What do we do?
- 我们该怎么办？
- I got this.
- 我有办法。
- Just show me what's in your shirt!
- 就给我看看你衬衫里有什么！
Ow!
哎哟！
What are you up to?
你在搞什么鬼？
- Commence phase two.
- 开始第二阶段。
[computer beeps]
[电脑蜂鸣声]
- Help!
- 救命！
- Okay, you stay right here.
- 好的，你待在这里别动。
Coming, Hazel!
来了，Hazel！
Oh. Ow! Okay--all right--
哦。哎哟！好吧——好吧——
- Where's the jersey? - It's right over--
- 球衣在哪儿？ - 就在——
- Hey, isn't this Dad's jersey?
- 嘿，这不是爸爸的球衣吗？
- Nope! - Wait, let me see the jersey.
- 不是！ - 等等，让我看看球衣。
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
- I'm tellin' Dad if you don't give me the jersey! - Dicky, go long!
- 如果你不把球衣给我，我就告诉爸爸！ - Dicky，跑远点！
- Who's ready for onion-y goodness?
- 谁准备好享受洋葱的美味了？
[gasps]
[喘气声]
No!
不！
What have they done to you?
他们对你做了什么？
- It was an accident. - We're really sorry, Dad.
- 这是个意外。 - 我们真的很抱歉，爸爸。
- Don't apologize to me.
- 别向我道歉。
Apologize to her!
向她道歉！
- We're really sorry, jersey?
- 我们真的很抱歉，球衣？
- Well, we were just fighting over the dog's name and-- - Oh, big surprise!
- 嗯，我们只是在争论狗的名字，然后-- - 哦，真是大惊小怪！
See, I thought you guys were finally working together,
看，我以为你们终于开始合作了，
but you weren't.
但你们没有。
Of course!
当然！
- You're right.
你说得对。
We screwed up, just like we always do.
我们搞砸了，就像我们总是那样。
I guess this means--
我想这意味着——
Goodbye, little guy.
再见，小家伙。
I'll miss you.
我会想你的。
- [howling]
（嚎叫声）
- Sorry, buddy.
对不起，伙计。
I just wish we'd come up with a better plan.
我只是希望我们能想出一个更好的计划。
- What plan?
- 什么计划？
- Well, after the dog peed on the jersey,
- 嗯，狗在球衣上撒尿后，
we thought we could clean it...
我们以为可以清洗它...
- So Nicky and I ran home,
- 所以尼基和我跑回家，
but you were there, so we had to go to the laundromat...
但你在家，所以我们只好去自助洗衣店...
- And we washed the signature off...
- 结果我们把签名洗掉了...
- And then you showed up and I hit Hazel with snowballs... - And no matter what we did, we just made things worse.
- 然后你出现了，我还用雪球打了黑兹尔... - 无论我们怎么做，情况只是变得更糟。
- So you guys did all this together?
- 所以你们一起做了这些？
- Well, yeah. We couldn't have kept it a secret all day by ourselves.
- 嗯，是的。我们自己一个人不可能整天保密。
- All day?
- 一整天？
You kept this from us all day?
你们一整天都瞒着我们？
Oh!
哦！
I am so proud of you!
我真为你感到骄傲！
- This is the strangest I've ever been yelled at.
这是我被骂得最奇怪的一次。
- But we ruined Dad's jersey and tried to cover it up.
但我们毁了爸爸的球衣，还试图掩盖。
- Yes, but you tried to cover it up together.
是的，但你们是一起试图掩盖的。
You lied to us as a team.
你们作为一个团队对我们撒了谎。
You were a united team of little liars.
你们是一群团结的小骗子。
It's not exactly what I had in mind,
虽然不是我原本设想的那样，
but I will take it!
但我接受这个结果！
- What's happening?
- 发生什么事了？
- I'll tell you what's happening.
- 我来告诉你发生了什么。
He's staying with us. - What?!
他要和我们住在一起。 - 什么？！
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
- Mega fireworks!
- 超级烟花！
[imitating explosions]
[模仿爆炸声]
- Awesome! We're not in trouble for ruining Dad's jersey!
- 太棒了！我们不会因为弄坏爸爸的球衣而惹上麻烦！
- Oh, no, you're in big trouble for that.
- 哦，不，你们会因为那件事惹上大麻烦。
- Who cares? We got our dog.
- 谁在乎呢？我们有了我们的狗。
- Harper huddle.
- Harper，集合。
All: Ah, Harper!
大家：啊，哈珀！
- Okay, I totally deserved that. Wow.
好的，我完全应得那个。哇。
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
[吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
[发出声音]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
[vocalizing]
[发出声音]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
- ♪
♪